

Samuel Cantrell

CONTACT Information 13346 SE Waldron Drive Milwaukie, OR 97222 mobile: (503) 406-8726 e-mail: samuelcantrell@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/samuelcantrell

TESTIMONIALS

"You will not find a person who is more eager to please, able to self-teach, and who can take delegration and run down the tasks assigned to him." — Dr. Bill Meade, Concordia University

"All you have to do is show [Sam] once and the rest is on auto-pilot... You will not be disappointed." — David Rich, CEO, Reitmeier Mechanical

"Samuel was one of the strongest students I have had in my finance classes in 10 years at Concordia University. His analytical skills are excellent and he can understand new information easily."

— Ron Miolla, Concordia University

Professional Experience

Concordia University, Portland, Oregon

Institutional Assessment Coordinator

May 2012 – present

- Developed Python scripts to automate preparation of data for analysis, saving time in the future.
- Designed reports relaying key performance indicators to school administration.

Brenner Tax and Bookkeeping, Milwaukie, Oregon

Accounting Intern

June 2010 - present

- Debugged check printing module for TheOS BASIC accounting system.
- Prepared financial statements for clients with speed and accuracy.
- Prepared payrolls and Oregon quarterly payroll tax reports for clients.

Reitmeier Mechanical, Tualatin, Oregon

Accounting Intern

May 2011 - August 2011

- Created data for identifying sales opportunities using company databases.
- Modified Sage Timberline Enterprise reports to meet specified requirements.

EDUCATION

Concordia University, Portland, Oregon

B.A. in Business Administration; Concentration in Accounting

August 2009 – present

- Expected graduation date: December 2012
- Minors: Finance, Music
- Overall GPA: 3.79
- Will have requisite number of credit hours to sit for CPA exam upon graduation.

Conducted successful redesign of school newspaper as layout editor. Awarded President's Premier Scholarship on merit.

Computer Knowledge

Familiar with:

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, etc.)
- Microsoft Windows
- GNU/Linux
- Python programming language